# **HYUNJAE WOO**

hjwoo@umich.edu

https://jaejaywoo.github.io

# RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interest is in the intersection of deep learning and reinforcement learning (RL) and its various real-world applications such as robotics. Specifically, I am interested in building efficient and task-agnostic intelligent machine through hierarchical RL and meta-learning.

### **EDUCATION**

# University of Michigan - Ann Arbor

Sep 2013 - Present

B.S.E. in Computer Science & Engineering (resolved the duty for military service: 2014 - 2015)

# **PUBLICATIONS**

Meta Reinforcement Learning with Autonomous Inference of Subtask Dependencies Sungryull Sohn, Hyunjae Woo, Jongwook Choi, Honglak Lee In the International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR), 2020

### RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

# Deep Learning Lab @ Univ. of Michigan

Oct 2018 - Present

Undergraduate Research Assistant

Advisor: Honglak Lee

- Implemented various RL baseline models such as hierarchical A2C algorithm using PyTorch and meta-evaluated the baselines against novel meta-hierarchical RL agent with autonomous task inference module on challenging RL environments such as StarCraft II Learning Environment (SC2LE) and The House Of inteRactions (THOR). The work is accepted at the ICLR 2020.
- Developed challenging game scenarios with complex and hierarchical dependencies in SC2LE

# Univ. of Michigan Transportation Research Institute

Jan 2019 - May 2019

Undergraduate Research Assistant

Advisor: Byoung-Keon (Daniel) Park

- Developed a stable version of TCP packet reader in C# that uses Pcap.Net (.NET wrapper for WinPcap) to convert TCP packets into CSV files.
- Collected various LiDAR datasets (TCP packets) for several road lanes with different materials to measure their robustness against severe weather conditions over time in Michigan.

# Reinforcement Learning Lab @ Univ. of Michigan

Oct 2017 - Sep 2018

Undergraduate Research Assistant

Advisor: Satinder Singh

- Implemented various deep RL algorithms such as A2C (with and without RNN) and hierarchical RL algorithms such as Option-Critic (with Deliberation Cost) in TensorFlow and evaluated the algorithms on SC2LE.
- Attended Blizzard × DeepMind StarCraft II Workshop @ Anaheim, CA with other undergraduate colleagues and interacted with world-leading researchers working on SC2LE.

# Vision and Learning Lab @ Seoul National Univ.

May 2017 - Aug 2017

Summer Research Intern Advisor: Gunhee Kim

- Implemented deep learning baseline algorithms (i.e. Im2txt and Seq2seq) for the *personalized* image captioning task and evaluated them on the large scale multi-media dataset Yahoo Flickr Creative Commons 100 Million (YFCC100M).
- Presented on the overview of *non-task oriented* (or *conversational*) dialogue system evaluation methods and potential future directions during the lab discussion.

### AWARDS AND HONORS

University Honors	2016
Dean's Honor List	2013, 2016
George Washington University SEAS Engineering Awards	2013

### SOFTWARE PROJECTS

### Fire Detection

Implemented an YOLO-v2 detection algorithm that can detect the instance of fire in the video by importing the pre-trained weights and training it on the new fire image datasets collected by our team.

## **Facial-Image Sentiment Classification**

Analyzed the facial image dataset through K-means algorithm and implemented autoencoder and convolutional neural networks (CNN) for classification.

# Recycle.it

Developed a eco-friendly, camera-based progressive web application using React.js. The application scans a barcode of a product and informs the user with helpful recycling information.

# TSP with Approximation and Optimization Algorithm

Implemented MST approximation and Branch-and-Bound optimization algorithms to several Traveling Salesman Problems (TSP) to create an optimal curcuit path to all the nodes.

# RELEVANT COURSES

Computer Science	Mathematics
EECS498: Reinforcement Learning	MATH217: Linear Algebra
EECS442: Intro to Computer Vision	MATH451: Advanced Calculus
EECS445: Intro to Machine Learning	MATH425: Intro to Probability
EECS492: Intro to Artificial Intelligence	MATH412: Intro to Modern Algebra

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

Machine Learning Libraries	Tensorflow, PyTorch, Keras
Programming Languages	Python, C/C++, C#, Javascript
Operating Systems	Linux, Unix